Finding Aid for National Archive on Sino-American Relations records, 1971-1984
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Americans in China 1971-1980
  - Yang, Chen-ning (Box 16)
  - Yang, Jen-Tsi (Box 16)
  - Yang, Richard (Box 16)
  - Yang, Winston (Box 16)
  - Yao, Margaret (Box 16)
  - Yeh, Kung-Chie (Box 16)
  - Zinder, Norton D. (Box 16)
  - Ziv, Bernard Jr. (Box 16)
  - Zumalt, Elmo, Jr. (Box 16)
  - Zweig, David (Box 16)
- Oral interviews, transcripts, and other sound recordings
  - Philadelphia Orchestra Visit to China
    (no attributed quotations without the permission of the interviewee)
    - Cassette tapes of interviews regarding visit to China 1973 (Box 16)
    - Note cards (arranged by broad topic) made from the taped interviews; also related correspondence and reports (Box 17)
  - United States Table Tennis Association
    - Cassette tapes of interviews regarding visit to China (Box 18)
      (restricted access in part)
    - Transcripts of interviews with members of the USTTA team to the People's Republic of China
      - Berris, Jan Carol (Box 28)
        [Restricted; no release form]
      - Edwards, Vee-Ling (Box 19)
      - Harrison, J. Rufford (Box 19)
      - Resek, Jairie (Box 19)
      - Steenhoven, Graham (Box 19)
      - Sweeris, Connie (Box 19)
    - Notes and correspondence re: other interviews
      - Bochenski, Judy (Box 19)
        also partial transcript
      - Boggan, Tim (Box 19)
      - Brathwaite, George (Box 19)
      - Buben, George and Madeline (Box 19)
      - Duranso, James (Box 19)
      - Howard, Jack (Box 19)
      - Jamieson, John (Box 19)
      - Kaminsky, (Mr. and Mrs. Y.) (Box 19)
      - Tannehill, John (Box 19)
    - Miscellanea re: oral interview project
      - Outline for interviews with Sweeris, Resek, and Bochenski (Box 19)
      - Addresses of interviewees (Box 19)
      - Itinerary, etc. of table tennis team (Box 19)
      - Diary of Anthony Shaheen containing his comments and impressions of the interviewees (Box 28)
  - Cassette tapes of reminiscences, speeches, debriefings, etc. (Box 21)
- Administrative and Background files
  - Project card files (Box 22)
  - Newspaper editorials on China-US relations 1973-1979, 15 folders (Box 23)
  - Administrative files, including survey forms, drafts of bibliography (Box 24)
- Visual materials
  - Photographs and slides
    - Abourezk, James 1978, 740 slides color (Box 25)
    - Allen, Steve 1975, 17 photographs black and white (Box 25)
    - Bacon, Margaret 1972, 100 slides color (Box 25)
    - Browne, Millard 1972, 268 slides color (Box 25)
    - China Features 1975-1976, 115 photographs black and white (Box 25)
    - Chollar, Robert G. 1975, 240 slides color (Box 26)
    - Coon, David P. 1978, 14 photographs color (Box 26)
    - Hays, Howard 1978, 70 photographs color (Box 26)
    - Herbert, Victor 1979, 6 slides color (Box 26)
    - Hsu, Kai-yu 1973, 8 prints; 48 photographs black and white (Box 26)
    - Huang, Su-shu 1974, 103 slides color (Box 26)
    - Janey, Jane 1979, 3 photographs color; 65 slides color (Box 26)
    - Knuth, Jill 1977, 22 slides color (Box 26)
    - Kroutil, Wayne 1979, 14 slides color (Box 26)
    - Lampton, Michael 1976, 80 photographs black and white (Box 26)
    - Lenchuk, Paul 1977, 73 slides color (Box 26)
    - Malt, Ronald 1973, 110 slides color (Box 26)
    - Menzel, Donald 1974, 6 photographs (Box 26)
    - Papper, Emmanuel M. 1974, 195 slides color (Box 26)
    - Pryor, Mary 1977, 18 photographs (Box 26)
    - Spencer, Donald C. 1973, 34 prints color (Box 26)
    - Swan, David 1975, 81 photographs black and white (Box 26)
  - Films and videocassettes
    - Burnham, Donald C. 1973, 3 reels; Super-8 sound film (Box 27)
    - Casey, Kenneth L. 1974, U-matic (3/4") videocassette (Box 27)
    - Coon, David P. 1978, U-matic (3/4") videocassette (Box 27)
    - Steenhoven, Graham 1971, 16mm film
      - "Chinese Ping Pong", color internegative and negative sound track (Box 27)
      - "U.S.Table Tennis Team in China", black and white original, dupe negative, and answer print (Box 27)